<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on Introduction</title><link>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on Introduction</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Google Summer of Code</title><link>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/gsoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/gsoc/</guid><description> Feedback Sharing Module in Commons App The Wikimedia Commons Android app allows users to upload pictures from their Android phone/tablet to Wikimedia Commons. This project aimed at sharing feedback about uploaded photos, educating people about topic &amp;amp; copyright and adding some sort of gamification to drive engagement. This project was implemented in two phases-
1) Feedback Created a new module to display feedback. Fetched and displayed following metrics using REST api on Common application- Number of images used in Wikipedia/Wikivoyage/etc articles Number of images that have been edited by someone else Number of images that have been featured Received barnstars Received thanks if the feature becomes available on Commons Added Gamification to the module in the form of levels and badges 2) Tutorial Created a quiz for users who have a high upload revert rate Added support to display the tutorial again for users who have a high upload revert rate</description></item><item><title>IBM Mentorship Program</title><link>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/ibm-mentorship-program/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/ibm-mentorship-program/</guid><description>IBM Global Remote Mentorship Program I was part of the team which undertook a project to improve the efficiency of neural architectures for comprehension-based question answering. Under the advisory of Dr. Kuntal Dey (Technology R&amp;amp;D Senior Principal at Accenture Technology, formerly (Advisory Research Scientist at IBM Research) and Seema Nagar (Advisory Research Scientist at IBM Research), we created a neural pipeline to translate the linguistically complex sentences of the Stanford Question-Answering dataset into simple sentences.</description></item><item><title>PersonaBot</title><link>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/chatbot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/chatbot/</guid><description>The chatbots currently being used are very domain-specific. Through the project, we try to create a general-purpose chatbot. We fine-tuned pre-trained a GPT-based architecture on PERSONA-CHAT dataset released by Facebook AI team in 2018. It is a crowd-sourced dataset consisting of 162,064 utterances collected from crowd workers working in Amazon Mechanical Turk. Several crowd-workers were paired randomly, and each group was asked to condition their conversations based on a given persona.</description></item></channel></rss>