<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction</title><link>https://tanvidadu.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Introduction</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tanvidadu.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Google Summer of Code</title><link>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/gsoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/gsoc/</guid><description>Sometimes I take picture Created two new modules, the Feedback Sharing Module to provide a brief feedback of the images uploaded, and the Quiz module for users who have a high percentage of their uploads deleted. Both modules were included in the v2.8 release of the Wikimedia Commons App. They can currently be accessed by going to the Settings and opting in as a Beta Tester of these new features.</description></item><item><title>IBM Mentorship Program</title><link>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/ibm-mentorship-program/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/ibm-mentorship-program/</guid><description>Sometimes I take picture Created two new modules, the Feedback Sharing Module to provide a brief feedback of the images uploaded, and the Quiz module for users who have a high percentage of their uploads deleted. Both modules were included in the v2.8 release of the Wikimedia Commons App. They can currently be accessed by going to the Settings and opting in as a Beta Tester of these new features.</description></item><item><title>ChatBot</title><link>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/chatbot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/chatbot/</guid><description>Chatbots are often used online and in messaging apps, but are also now included in many operating systems as intelligent virtual assistants, such as Siri for Apple products and Cortana for Windows. Dedicated chatbot appliances are also becoming increasingly common, such as Amazon’s Alexa. These chatbots can perform a wide variety of functions based on user commands. Non-goal-oriented dialogue systems (chatbots) are an interesting test-bed for interactive Natural Language Processing (NLP) systems and are also directly useful in a wide range of applications ranging from technical support services to entertainment.</description></item><item><title>Cross-lingual Inductive Transfer to Detect Offensive Language</title><link>https://tanvidadu.github.io/blog/offenseevalsemeval2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tanvidadu.github.io/blog/offenseevalsemeval2020/</guid><description>With the growing use of social media and its availability, many instances of the use of offensive language have been observed across multiple languages and domains. This phenomenon has given rise to the growing need to detect the offensive language used in social media cross-lingually. In OffensEval 2020, the organizers have released the multilingual Offensive Language Identification Dataset (mOLID), which contains tweets in five different languages, to detect offensive language. In this work, we introduce a cross-lingual inductive approach to identify the offensive language in tweets using the contextual word embedding XLM-RoBERTa (XLM-R).</description></item><item><title>Towards Code-switched Classification Exploiting Constituent Language Resources</title><link>https://tanvidadu.github.io/blog/codeswitchsrw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tanvidadu.github.io/blog/codeswitchsrw/</guid><description>Code-switching is a commonly observed communicative phenomenon denoting a shift from one language to another within the same speech exchange. The analysis of code-switched data often becomes an assiduous task, owing to the limited availability of data. In this work, we propose converting code-switched data into its constituent high resource languages for exploiting both monolingual and cross-lingual settings. This conversion allows us to utilize the higher resource availability for its constituent languages for multiple downstream tasks.</description></item><item><title>Sarcasm Detection using Context Separators in Online Discourse</title><link>https://tanvidadu.github.io/blog/sarcasmdetect/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tanvidadu.github.io/blog/sarcasmdetect/</guid><description>Sarcasm is an intricate form of speech, where meaning is conveyed implicitly. Being a convoluted form of expression, detecting sarcasm is an assiduous problem. The difficulty in recognition of sarcasm has many pitfalls, including misunderstandings in everyday communications, which leads us to an increasing focus on automated sarcasm detection. In the second edition of the Figurative Language Processing (FigLang 2020) workshop, the shared task of sarcasm detection released two datasets, containing responses along with their context sampled from Twitter and Reddit.</description></item><item><title>Towards Detection of Subjective Bias using Contextualized Word Embeddings</title><link>https://tanvidadu.github.io/blog/subjectivebiaswww/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tanvidadu.github.io/blog/subjectivebiaswww/</guid><description>Subjective bias detection is critical for applications like propaganda detection, content recommendation, sentiment analysis, and bias neutralization. This bias is introduced in natural language via inflammatory words and phrases, casting doubt over facts, and presupposing the truth. In this work, we perform comprehensive experiments for detecting subjective bias using BERT-based models on the Wiki Neutrality Corpus (WNC). The dataset consists of 360k labeled instances, from Wikipedia edits that remove various instances of the bias.</description></item><item><title>BERT-based Ensembles for Modeling Disclosure and Support in Conversational Social Media Text.</title><link>https://tanvidadu.github.io/blog/affcon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tanvidadu.github.io/blog/affcon/</guid><description>There is a growing interest in understanding how humans initiate and hold conversations. The affective understanding of conversations focuses on the problem of how speakers use emotions to react to a situation and to each other. In the CL-Aff Shared Task, the organizers released Get it #OffMyChest dataset, which contains Reddit comments from casual and confessional conversations, labeled for their disclosure and supportiveness characteristics. In this paper, we introduce a predictive ensemble model exploiting the finetuned contextualized word embeddings, RoBERTa and ALBERT.</description></item></channel></rss>