<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Creations on Tanvi Dadu</title><link>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/creations/</link><description>Recent content in Creations on Tanvi Dadu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 15:00:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/creations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Google Summer of Code: Feedback on how pictures uploaded to Commons get used</title><link>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/creations/gsoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/creations/gsoc/</guid><description/></item><item><title>PERSONABOT : PERSON OR MACHINE</title><link>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/creations/personabot/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/creations/personabot/</guid><description>Chatbots are often used online and in messaging apps, but are also now included in many operating systems as intelligent virtual assistants, such as Siri for Apple products and Cortana for Windows. Dedicated chatbot appliances are also becoming increasingly common, such as Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Alexa. These chatbots can perform a wide variety of functions based on user commands. Non-goal-oriented dialogue systems (chatbots) are an interesting test-bed for interactive Natural Language Processing (NLP) systems and are also directly useful in a wide range of applications ranging from technical support services to entertainment.</description></item><item><title>DERMADOC: THE SKIN SPECIALIST APPLICATION</title><link>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/creations/dermahack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/creations/dermahack/</guid><description>It’s a common practice among people to refer the internet or various easily accessible resources before they consult a doctor. This can often create a sense of panic and confusion if the sources are not reliable. In the case of skin diseases, where it might be very hard to describe the exact condition through verbal description, diagnosis through image recognition could be the future of skin disease detection. There already exist some applications which diagnose skin diseases through the textual description provided by the user.</description></item><item><title>IMAGE FORGERY DETECTION APP</title><link>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/creations/deepfake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tanvidadu.github.io/projects/creations/deepfake/</guid><description>Developed an Android application to detect fake human images.It differentiates GAN-generated face-images from real face-images.Methodology involved training ResNet-50 model on a publicly available datasetThe proposed architecture had an accuracy of 90%The trained model was deployed on a Django-based API and made available via Android application.</description></item></channel></rss>